A Guide to the Photographs, Series 1011-1081 FA438
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Downtown Lower Manhattan Association, 1937-1995; 1081; 7 Cubic Feet 16 manuscript boxes (approximately 1100 prints and 900 slides)
  - Slides, 3
    - Waterfront (including South Street Seaport), Other Formats: 17 slides (Box 15, Folder 249)
  - Audio and Visual Materials, 4
    - Lower Manhattan Demolition and New Buildings, July-October 1968; Silent __Super 8 Film.; 1 film reel (Box 16, Folder 250)
      Film includes a live cattle demonstration in front of the Chemical Bank Building, with cow milking, Animal Science Department, New York State College of Agriculture.
    - Lower Manhattan Demolition and New Buildings, July-October 1968; VHS copy transferred from the Super 8 film. Silent. (Box 16, Folder 0250A)
      Material Specific Details note
      Scholarly Access is provided to the VHS access copy.
    - Sound Recording - Presentation at 15th Anniversary of D-LMA, June 7, 1973, 4PM; __41:18 __Original sound recording is on a 3 3/4ips sound reel. (Box 16, Folder 251)
      Meeting held at Chase Manhattan Building, Auditorium A. Speakers include: A. John Lindsey (New York City Mayor) B. David Rockefeller C. Edward F. Wagner - Presentation of D-LMA Fourth Report. [Wagner also read a telegram from Governor Nelson A. Rockefeller who could not attend this meeting.]
    - Sound Recording on Compact Disc - Presentation at 15th Anniversary of D-LMA, June 7, 1973, 4PM; CD copy transferred from the 3 3/4ips sound reel. __41:18 (Box 16, Folder 0251A)
      Scholarly access is provided to the version the CD access copy.
      Downtown Lower Manhattan Association, Inc. (DLMA)
    - Sound Recording - "The People Problem" - WBZ Radio Program, No date; One 7 1/2 ips monophonic recording (1 track). (Box 16, Folder 252)
    - "Lower Manhattan" [VHS] [a Cresta video souvenir] (Box 16, Folder 253)
      Sponsored by: Association for a Better New York and D-LMA, Inc.